BRIAN CHILDS

GRAPHIC ARTIST & FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

An experienced Graphic Artist with a newly obtained completion certificate from the University of Denver's Full Stack Coding Bootcamp. I have a passion for creating professional designs and userfriendly applications. I'm also a versatile team player with proven success in management, customer service and crossteam collaboration. I'm a flexible. fast learner bringing curiosity and passion to every project.

GKILLG

| 2 VILL 2 | |
|------------------|------|
| HTML | *** |
| CSS | **** |
| Bootstrap | **** |
| Wordpress | **** |
| Javascript | **** |
| Jquery | **** |
| Node | **** |
| MySQL | *** |
| Google Dev Tools | *** |
| VS Code | **** |
| React | *** |
| Express | *** |
| Photoshop | **** |
| Illustrator | **** |
| Indesign | **** |
| Acrobat | **** |
| After Effects | *** |
| Premier | *** |
| Dreamweaver | *** |
| Mail Chimp | *** |
| Apple | **** |
| PC | **** |

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE GRAPHIC ARTIST PETROLIA MARKETING

2017—PRESENT ENGLEWOOD. CO

Freelance graphic artist /marketing business owner with vast experience in developing professional designs, strong customer relationships, meeting strict deadlines and making all business decisions. Including project and time management, conflict resolution, leadership, adaptability, teamwork and creativity as an acting business owner and operator.

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

- ◆ Creating multiple brands from conceptualization to digital and print deliverables.
- ◆ Developing and implementing marketing strategies for small business.
- ◆ Performance bonus Automotive Internet Marketing.
- ◆ Graphic Design, UX/UI, Large format design and Print Production services for small business.

DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER

2015-2016

MEDICAL SALES COLLEGE

LITTLETON. CO

Developed, implemented, and tracked digital marketing campaigns for social media and online presence. Identified trends and optimized performance resulting in followers and higher enrollment.

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

- ◆ Developed LinkedIn and Twitter pages resulting in thousands of followers.
- ◆ Marketing led to higher enrollments and eventually more campuses.

ART DIRECTOR / PROJECT MANAGER

2012-2015

XL EDGE ENGLEWOOD. CO

Art Director and Project Manager responsibilities, conceptual design for digital and print marketing, production schedule management for monthly publication.

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

- ◆ Promoted and managed 3 people and production schedule.
- ◆ Worked with large brands like General Mills, Kraft, Unilever and Kroger.

GRAPHIC ARTIST / PRINT PRODUCTION

2010-2011 DENVER. CO

ALPHGRAHICS

Production Graphic Artist for print marketing and large format.

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS:

- ◆ Designed and produced large format prints on many different types of media.
- ◆ Developed production skills and worked on projects from concepts to deliverables.

GRAPHIC ARTIST / PRINT PRODUCTION

2007-2010

COTTRELL PRINTING

ENGLEWOOD. CO

Production/Design on Demand Graphic Artist in a fast paced, tight deadline environment. **KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS:**

- ◆ Learned Adobe Creative Suite and used Photoshop, Illustrator and Indesign daily.
- ◆ USPS certification for designing mail.

EDUCATION

BOOTCAMP CERTIFICATE: DENVER UNIVERSITY

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

BACHELOR'S DEGREE: COLORADO INSTITUTE OF ART

A Graphic Design and Visual Communications Major.

Classes included: Art Direction, Drawing, Typography, Video Editing and Multimedia and Printing Design.